United Tenants of Albany apap118
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001, 5; 1.5 cubic ft.
  - Affordable Housing, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 7)
  - Affordable Housing, News Clippings and Press Releases, April 18, 1972- January 4, 1990, 1972-1990 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 8)
  - Affordable Housing, News Clippings, March 7, 1990- October 15, 1995, 1990-1995 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 9)
  - Affordable Housing, Newsletters, 1981-1992 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 10)
  - Affordable Housing, Ad Hoc Committee on Housing Statement on Housing and Action Plan, December 6, 1983 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 11)
  - Affordable Housing, News Clippings, 1973-1989 (Box 2 (Continued) (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 12)
  - Affordable Housing, List of Elderly Housing Capital District, 1979 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 1)
  - Affordable Housing, Public Utility Law Project Lawsuit Concerning Amendment Line-Extension Rules, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 2)
  - Bank Challenge, Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 3)
  - Bank Challenge, News Clippings, 1980-1990 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 4)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 5)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 6)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Housing Code Violations, 1976-1980 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 7)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Code Violators of the Week, Month and Year, 1976 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 8)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Legislation, 1976, 1978, 1986 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 9)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Real Property Laws, Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 10)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Real Property Laws, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 1)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Real Property Laws, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 2)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 3)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Real Property Laws, Publications, 1999-2001 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 4)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Strategies, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 5)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, News Clippings, 1977 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 6)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, News Clippings, 1975-1991 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 7)
  - Effective Code Enforcement, Newsletters and Press Releases, 1971-1978 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 8)
  - Homesteading, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 9)
  - Homesteading, Newsletters and Press Releases, 1971, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 10)
  - Public Housing Elections, Information on Election Tenant Commissioners, 1982 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 11)
  - Rent Control, Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 12)
  - Rent Control, Meetings Coalition for Fair Rents, 1979-1983 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 13)
  - Rent Control, Pamphlets and Fact Sheets, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 1)
  - Rent Control, Pamphlets and Fact Sheets, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 2)
  - Rent Control, Fact Sheets, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 3)
  - Rent Control, News Clippings, 1971-1991 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 4)
  - Rent Control, Press Releases, 1975, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 5)
  - Rent Control, Newsletters, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 6)
  - Rent Control, Legislation, 1975-1982 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 7)
  - Rent Control, Legislation, 1982-1984 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 8)
  - Tenants' Advice and Rights, Advice to Tenants, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 9)
  - Tenants' Advice and Rights, Information Coalition Tenant's Rights, undated, 1972-2001 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 10)
  - Tenants' Advice and Rights, Information Coalition Mobile Home Owners and Tenants, 1975, 1985, 1988 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files, 1971-1992, 1995, 1999-2001), Folder 11)